Henry DeWolf Smyth Papers 1885-1987 Mss.Ms.Coll.15
American Philosophical Society
- Series XV. Memorabilia, 1914-1979
  - Nuclear Statesman Award. Medal for the, 15 Nov. 1972
  - Office of Research and Development. Certificate of merit, 1945
  - Postcards
    - Folder #1-2, n.d.
      blank
  - Princeton University. Diploma, 1918
  - Princeton University. Diploma, 1920
  - Princeton University. Diploma, 1921
  - Princeton University Graduate School. Ph.D. record, 1921
  - Smyth family tree, n.d.
    by HDS
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers., 4 Jul. 1944
    Manhattan Engineer District
    HDS I.D. card
  - U.S. AEC Citation, n.d.
    medal
  - U.S. Department of State, 1970
    Distinguished Honor Award. Medal of the
  - University of Cambridge. Acceptance certificate, 9 Feb. 1924
  - University of Gottingen, 1931
  - Wedding anniversary. 34th, 30 Jun. 1970
  - Woodrow Wilson Award. Certificate of the, 22 Feb. 1964
- Oversize Box 1 - Series I to XIV
  - Series I-II
    - Ser. I, Professional Correspondence
      - -Mallinckrodt, Edward, Jr., 1954-55
      - -Princeton University Committee on Project Research and Inventions, Folder #5, 1958
    - Ser. II, General Subject Files
      - -Faraday celebrations, 1931
      - -Maxwell Centenary Celebration. James Clerk, 1931
      - -Princeton University. OSRD project SSRC-5. Contract OEMsr-260, n.d.
      - -Princeton University. OSRD project SSRC-5. Miscellaneous data, 1942
      - -Princeton University Weekly Bulletin, 1920; 1921; 1926
      - -Theoretical Aspects. Conference of Sub-Committee on, n.d.
        charts
  - Series III-XII
    - Ser. III, AEC Subject Files
      - -Reactor Policies and Programs, Ad Hoc Advisory Committee on, 1958
    - Ser. IV, IAEA Subject Files
      - -Organizational chart, 1961
    - Ser. VIII, Manuscripts of Published Works
      - -Smyth Report. The, 1976
        Princ. U. Lib. Chron. pg. proofs
      - -Stopping the atomic armament race: what we are up against, 1946
        "Atlantic Monthly" art.
  - Series XIII, Clippings
    - Folder #1
      - -AEC, 1954
      - -Einstein, Albert, 1939; 1959
    - Folder #2
      - -European Defense Community Conference, 1954
      - -[Japanese newspaper], 1957
      - -Oppenheimer clearance #10, 1954
      - -Oppenheimer obituaries, 1967
  - Series XIV, Photographs
    - -AEC. Group photos Dean, Gordon Lilienthal, David Strauss, Lewis L. [Wilson, Arnold L.?], n.d.
      4 total
    - -de Coningh, E. H., n.d.
    - -de Coningh, Virginia, 1946
      [Ginny]
    - -Emerson, Mary de Coningh, 1951
    - -Frank, Virginia de Coningh, n.d.
      [Ginna]
    - -Johnson, Lyndon B., 1967
      photo. signed
    - -Smyth, H. D., n.d.
      3 total
    - -Smyth, H. D., n.d.
      uniden. groups, 2 total
    - -Smyth, Mary de Coningh, [1936]
      wedding photo
  - Series XV, Memorabilia
    - -DeWolf, Delos. Residence of, n.d.
    - -NiederC6sterreich, Lower Austria, Basse-Autriche, 1970
    - -Nuclear Statesman Award. Certificate of the, 1972
- Oversize Box 2 - Misc. Formats (Oversize 2-Misc. Formats)
  - Series II, Lord & Taylor Award, 1957
    scrapbook
  - Series XIII, Atomic bomb scrapbooks
    - Folder #1, 6-24 Aug. 1945
    - Folder #2, 27 Aug. 1945-3 Apr. 1946
  - Series XV, Memorabilia
    - -American Philosophical Society. Membership certificate, 1947
    - -Lawrenceville School. Alpha Delta Tau diploma, 13 Jul. 1914
    - -Lawrenceville School. Diploma, 8 Jun. 1914
    - -National Research Council. Appointment certificate, Oct. 1921
    - -Princeton University. Diploma, 1918
    - -Princeton University. Diploma, 1920
    - -Princeton University. Diploma, 1921
    - -University of Cambridge. Acceptance certificate, 9 Feb. 1924